http://www.carbideprocessors.com/pages/company-info/privacy-policy.html

Incra
Kant Twist (Clamp Manufacturing Co)
Bondhus
Clamp Manufacturing Co.
0
Loading... Please wait...
Carbide Processors, Woodworking Tools
We're here to help! Give us a call at:
(800) 346-8274
Search
Free Ground Shipping on Orders over $150!Over 23,000 Items Discounts up to 40% off Retail
Blog
Company Info
Terms & ConditionsProduct ReviewsFrequently Asked Questions Contact UsOnline SecurityPrivacy PolicyShippingReturnsAbout Us
Media
NewslettersCarbide Processors BlogOnline ArticlesBooks Video LibraryMagazine ArticlesCarbide Saw Manual
Woodworks
Technical Info
WoodworkingCarbide PartsGrinding Carbide- Health and safety risksBrazing CarbideRouter BitsSaw BladesTypes of Drill BitsMachine Coolant
Custom Tooling
Catalogs
BesseyBondhusFELOHuotOshlunPopular ToolsSGSSoutheast ToolTenryuTriumph Twist DrillVortexWera Stainless Steel ToolsWera ScrewdriversWera RatchetsWera L-KeysWera Kraftform KompaktWera BitsWera Torque ToolsWhiteside MachineWiha BitsWiha ESDWiha HexWiha InsulatedWiha PliersWiha ScrewdriversWiha Shop ToolsWiha Tech ToolsWiha Torque ControlWiha Torx
Basic Carbide Saw Tip Information and How To Order
Tom's Tools
Router Tools
Categories
Clamps
Drill Press Tables
Routers
Router Bits
Incra
Kant Twist (Clamp Manufacturing Co)
M. Power
Milescraft
Woodpecker Tools
Cutting Tools
Categories
Annular Cutters
Carbide Burs
Carbide End Mills
Bondhus
Clamp Manufacturing Co.
Felo
Innovative Tools
Klein Tools
Mayhew
Rennsteig
SOG
Triumph
Wera
Books
Braze Alloy (Silver Solder)
Carbide Burs
Carbide Saw Tips
Carbide STB Strips
Clamp - Fixture
CNC Parts and Accessories
Coolant Filtration
Supplies
Cutting Tool Storage
Privacy Policy
Quick version: We will not do anything with your information without your explicit permission.
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.Carbideprocessors.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following: 1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared. 2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data. 3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information. 4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
At Carbide Processors, we have a huge respect for your privacy. Third parties (such as AdRoll) may place cookies on your browser for targeted advertising purposes. Information collected may include IP addresses, cookie identifiers and website activity. You may opt out at Opt Out. We promise to not share your e-mail address, or any other customer information, with third parties. Your information is used, as necessary, to fulfill orders, keep you informed (if you wish) and for customer service. If you have any questions about the details of our privacy policy, please do not hesitate to contact us.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website: • See what data we have about you, if any. • Change/correct any data we have about you. • Have us delete any data we have about you. • Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Merchant Services
Home
Products
Services
About Us
Sitemap
Reviews Sitemap
Contact Us:1(800)346-8274
All prices are in USD Copyright 2020 Carbide Processors. Sitemap |
Website by oBundle
